{
    "question": "How the rainbow is produced?\u200b",
    "attachments": [],
    "answers": [
        {
            "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><h3>Sunlight looks white. When sunlight hits and is reflected by water droplets, the light will be dispersed and widened so that the colors in the rainbow appear.</h3>",
            "attachments": []
        }
    ],
    "related_questions": [
        {
            "slug": "d-luna-what-do-you-think-of-the-scenery-here-maya-its-975",
            "question": "D. Luna : What do you think of the scenery here?    Maya : It's ........\r\n................ scenery I have ever seen.\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p></p><p>it&#039;s <u>the </u><u>best</u> scenery i have ever seen.</p><p></p><p>cmiiw</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "4-amara-was-sick-three-days-ago-362",
            "question": "4. (+) Amara was sick three days ago\r\n(-)\r\n(?)\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>(-)Amara was not sick three days ago</p><p>(?)was Amara sick three days ago</p><p></p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>&gt;//&lt;</p><p></p>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>(+) Amara was sick three days ago\n</p><p>(-) Amara \u00a0wasn&#039;t sick three days ago\n</p><p>(?)\u200b Was Amara sick three days ago? yes, she was. no, she wasn&#039;t</p><p></p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "a-person-who-behaves-iii-a-u-a-person-with-bad-manners-someone-wh-469",
            "question": "A person who behaves III a u    A person with bad manners\r\nSomeone who is not very talkative\r\nSomeone who is very tidy\r\nSomeone who is good at learning things\r\nA truthful person who doesn't cheat or st\r\nTask 10\r\nRearrange the jumbled words into a correct sentence!\r\nvery - she-me-is-to-kind\r\n1.\r\n2.\r\nbe-minded-close-don't-So\r\n3.\r\nyoung-she-woman-an-is-energetic\r\nwer\r\n4.\r\nhas - personality-an-she-outgoing\r\n4. Let's associate\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>1. she is very kind of me</p><p>2. don&#039;t be so close minded</p><p>3. she is an energetic young woman</p><p>4. she has an outgoing personality</p><p></p><p>semoga terbantu, maap kalo salah\u270c</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>1. very - she-me-is-to-kind</p><p>she is very kind to me</p><p>2. be-minded-close-don&#039;t-So</p><p>don&#039;t be so close minded</p><p>3.young-she-woman-an-is-energetic</p><p>she is an energetic young woman</p><p>4. has - personality-an-she-outgoing</p><p>she has an outgoing personality</p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>Idk whether its true or not, but  I hope it can help u, gudluck :)</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "b-qsc-d-gl-i-have-a-favorite-bancherh-my-school-he-is-mr-denl-656",
            "question": "B    QSC\r\nD. GL\r\nI have a favorite bancherh my school He is Mr. Denl. He is\r\nmy English facher. He is 30 years old. He is tall and\r\nhandsome. He has round eyes a pointed nose, and thick lips\r\nHe has straight har that always looks neat. He is the strict\r\nand discipline person. He also has bng mustache and beard\r\nfairy dense. His sun is brown. He is very diligent. He is also\r\nsmart and honest He oves must very much. He is very good\r\nat playing a guitar. He is a good person and we bve him very\r\nmuch\r\n\r\n12. How does he look like?\r\nA He has found eyes a flat nose, and thin lips. He has\r\nstraight hair\r\nB He hasslanteyes a pointed nose, and thick lips. He has\r\nC. He has found eyes, a pointed nose, and thick lips. He\r\nhas straight hair\r\nD. He has round eyes, a pointed nose, and thin lips. He has\r\ny hair\r\n13 How does he look like?\r\nA He has found eyes a fet nose, and thin lips. He has\r\nstraight hair\r\nB He has slant eyes a pointed nose, and thick lips. He has\r\nWavy hair\r\nC. He has round eyes, a pointed nose, and thick lps. He\r\nhas straight hair\r\nD. He has found eyes, a pointed nose, and thin lips. He has\r\n14.Deb\r\ncoo\r\nMrs\r\nis his skin brown?\r\nA Yes it's\r\nB No. is not\r\nC Yes. It does\r\nD. No. he is not\r\n15 What do you think about Mr. Dent?\r\nA He is very digort smart and honest person\r\nB Hois smart honest but lay person\r\nCHe is the strict but not discipline person\r\nD He is smart toucher but not discipline person\r\n16 A place where alrcraft magularly take off and land, with\r\nbuildings for passengers to waith\r\nA Gas Station\r\nB Train station\r\nC Arport\r\n17 Parking Ama many people standing outside the movie\r\nA There is\r\nB There are\r\nC There\r\nD Is there\r\n18 then a small cat playing with some toys\r\nA is\r\nB Are\r\nC Am\r\nD. Have\r\n19 We use this thing to cook our meals tsa\r\nA Basin\r\nB Stove\r\nC Rack\r\nD Knife\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>12. C. he has round eyes, a pointed nose, and thick lips. He has straight hair</p><p>13. C. he has round eyes, a pointed nose, and thick lips. He has straight hair</p><p>14. C. yes it does</p><p>15. A. he is very diligent, smart, and honest person</p><p>16. C. airport</p><p>17. B. there are</p><p>18. A. is</p><p>19. B. stove</p><p></p><p><strong>Semoga</strong><strong> </strong><strong>terbantu</strong><strong>,</strong><strong> </strong><strong>maap</strong><strong> </strong><strong>kalo</strong><strong> </strong><strong>salah</strong><strong>\u270c</strong></p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "13-penguapan-pada-tumbuhan-disebut-juga-transpirasi-b-kondensas-723",
            "question": "13. Penguapan pada tumbuhan    disebut juga\r\ntranspirasi\r\nb. kondensasi\r\nc. evaporasi\r\nd. revitalisasi\r\ntolong di jawab plis\r\n\r\n\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>a. transpirasi</p><p>Peristiwa berubahnya air menjadi uap dan bergerak dari permukaan tanah dan permukaan air ke udara disebut evaporasi (penguapan). <strong>Peristiwa penguapan dari tanaman disebut transpirasi</strong>. Kedua-duanya bersama-sama disebut Evapotranspirasi.</p><p>sumber:</p><p> https://ekaratnawati2492.wordpress.com/2012/11/14/transpirasi-pada-tumbuhan-2/#:~:text=Peristiwa%20berubahnya%20air%20menjadi%20uap%20dan%20bergerak%20dari,Evapotranspirasi.%20I.%20Kegunaan%20dan%20kerugian%20transpirasi%20terhadap%20tumbuhan.</p><p>semoga membantu!</p><p></p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "24-della-james-i-need-one-hundred-more-bed-shield-and-pillow-650",
            "question": "24. Della : \"James, I need one hundred more bed    shield and pillow cases of any color. Can\r\nyou deliver them this week?\u201d\r\nJames : \"Sure but the price is increasing about\r\n10%. Will you still make an order?\u201d\r\nDella : \"If that's so, I have to tell this to my\r\nboss. I'll give you a call after lunch.\"\r\nWhat is the woman going to do?\r\nA. Talk to her boss.\r\nB. Cancel the order.\r\nC. Buy the pillow.\r\nD. Ask for a discount.\r\nE. Look for another supplier.\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong><em><u>A. talk to her boss.</u></em></strong></p><p></p><p></p><p>............................</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p></p><p>a. talk to her boss</p><p></p><p>cmiiw ya</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "im-sorry-but-i-wont-be-able-meet-you-and-bertha-for-lunch-on-fr-799",
            "question": "I'm sorry but I won't be able meet you and bertha for lunch on friday.    what is the writer's reason canceled luch ?\r\nartinya\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>Saya minta maaf, karena saya tidak bisa datang untuk bertemu denganmu dan bertha untuk makan siang di hari jumat.</p><p>Apa alasan penulis membatalkan janjian makan siang?</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>Maaf tapi saya tidak bisa bertemu denganmu dan Bertha untuk makan siang di hari Jumat</p><p>Apa alasan si penulis membatalkan makan siangnya?</p><p> </p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "make-your-own-paragraph-about-your-activity-in-the-past-start-fr-886",
            "question": "Make your own paragraph about your activity in the past. start from 'a long time ago'\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p>a long time ago i was playing in the backyard. playing with mud and grass to be exactly, i ended up playing for 2 hours straight and imagining things, when i got up my whole outfit was under the mud. i had to take a shower</p><p></p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "14-today-toothache-15labdi-the-library-b-pe-read-16-safina-li-276",
            "question": "14. Today    toothache\r\n15.Labdi the library\r\nb. Pe\r\nRead\r\n16. Safina liver\r\nBrooch\r\nd. User\r\n17. Below are doors found in stationery SCE, CHOTE\r\na. Peagi\r\ne Shagede\r\n13. Wem shop for starts, trous and socks in the\r\na Bookstore\r\nb. Clothing Store\r\nc. Eladrone store\r\n&amp; Toys\r\n19. The meaning of coucha\r\n2. Batuk\r\nb. Salute\r\ne. Flu\r\nd. Sakit kepala\r\n20. The lang\r\na la\r\nb. On\r\nthe window and the bod (di antara).\r\nc. Between\r\nd. Opposite\r\n\r\ntolong d bantu jawabanya\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>13. B. clothing store</p><p>19. a. batuk</p><p>20. c. between</p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>nomor lainnya sy g paham maksud pertanyaan</p><p>maaf</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "look-at-the-body-of-the-latter-can-you-find-the-following-items-957",
            "question": "Look at the body of the latter. can you find the following items    a. the date\r\nb. the time\r\nc. the contact for RSV\r\nd. the dress code\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>D.Thw dress code</p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>Maaf kalo salah</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}